John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Dept. P: Scott - Books, 1/1/1925-12/31/1994 (Box 186)
    James Monroe 1758-1831 [book]; The Reader's Digest Dictionary of Quotations [book]; Tough Choice Who made them .. And who didn't, The Concord Coalition's Deficit Reduction Scorecard 103rd Congress 1993 [booklet]; Miracle on the Potomac, The Kennedy Center from the Beginning [book]; Billy Franklin's Tough Enough, The Cocaine Investigation of United States Senator Chuck Robb [book]; Fix Bayonets! [book]; Miracle at Philadelphia: The Story of the Constitutional Convention May to September 1787 [book]; The Hite Report on Male Sexuality [book]; Our American Government, What Is It? How Does It Function? 150 Questions and Answers (1981 Edition) [book]; America: An Affirmation of Faith [book]; A Search for the 100 Greatest Members of Congress, Heroes of the US Congress [book]; Eminent Americans: Namesakes of the Polaris Submarine Fleet [book]; Henry Cabot Lodge, Late a Senator from Massachusetts, Memorial Addresses Delivered in Congress [book]; Will the Gentleman Yield? [book]; Song and Service Book for Ship and Field [book]; Profiles in Courage [book]; Webster's Seventh New Collegiate Dictionary [book]; Pages From the Virginia Story [book]; The X Factor, A Quest For Excellence [book]; Jefferson, Public and Private Papers [book]; The New Fat Cats, Members of Congress as Political Benefactors [book]; Military Project Management Handbook [book]; Richmond Redeemed, The Siege at Petersburg [book]; The Battle of Berlin 1945 [book]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Releases, 1/1/1983-12/31/1988 (Box 187)
    ISTEA; Smart Road; Untitled Folder: Correspondence regarding ISTEA; Section 153; ISTEA; DOT Building; DOT; ISTEA II; ISTEA II-Transit; ISTEA Grants-Va.
  - Dept. L- BRAC Commission, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 94)
  - Dept. A: Various Files, 1/1/1993-12/31/2000 (Box 187)
    Press Releases, 1983 [binder]; Press Releases, 1988 [binder]; Press Releases, 1984 [binder]; Press Releases, 1987 [binder]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 4/1/1994-7/31/1994 (Box 188)
    14 folders of press clippings, arranged by chronologically by week
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 1/1/1994-4/30/1994 (Box 189)
    15 folders in no real order, clippings grouped by date.
  - Dept. P: Scott - Warner Speeches, 12/7/1982-9/14/1983 (Box 190)
    Untitled Folder: Remarks Before the conference banquet of the National Security Industrial Association Anti-Submarine Warfare committee; 5/18/83; Norfolk, Norfolk Chamber of Commerce; 4/29/83; Joe Canada Breakfast/Growing Conservatism/GOP Successes; 10/10/83; Transcript of Phone Interview tom Matthews/Kingsport Times Haysi, Coal Slurry, topping off; 6/30/83; Floor Statement - In Memory of Sen. Jackson; 9/14/83; Floor Statement - on Amendment To Transportation Conference Report H.R. 3329; 8/3/83; Confirmation Hearing/Judge Yock Judicial Committee; 7/22/83; Staunton-Augusta County Chamber of Comm. Dinner- Staunton, Va; 1/21/83; E & MR Subcommittee Hearing on S. 1634 Mineral Lands Leasing Act; 10/18/83; Public Hearing- HOV- Restrictions at Cutis Memorial Parkway- George Mason HS, FC, VA; 4/14/83; Interview- National Public Radio- Helen Whelan; 1/4/83; Transcript/Phone Interview with Chris Hansen, Reuters "Deep Strike concept"; 6/17/83; JWW Remarks/Federal Employees Forum- Old Dominion Univ., Norfolk; 10/22/83; Norfolk Chamber of Commerce; 4/30/83; Finance Committee/Governmental Lease Financing Reform Act Amendments; 9/29/83; Floor Statement - Insertion of Statement of ABA on Intelligence of Synfuels in Soviet Union; 5/16/83; Floor Statement - Dedication of the Memorial Plaque re Iranian Rescues Mission; 5/5/83; Speech Before Transportation Inst to minority bus members; 7/27/83; Transcript- Chris Callahan, Va. Network Telephone Network; 5/19/83; Va. American Legion Speech; 7/9/83; Remarks of JWW/National Coal Assoc., Wash, DC; 11/17/83; Floor Statement - IMF Loan Quota; 6/8/83; News Release on Harvey Wilkerson/4th Circuit Court Appointee; 11/12/83; Floor Statement - on SPR; 10/19/83; Floor Statement - Memory of Mary Preston Courtney; 12/13/82; Floor Statement - Honoring Harry F. Byrd, Jr.; 12/8/1982; Subcommittee Civil Service, Post Office, and General Services; 5/26/83; Confirmation Hearing/Judge Merow Judicial Committee; 7/22/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner/Amendment to Modify HOV Requirements on I-66; 10/24/83; Remarks: MTN. Empire Community Big Stone Gap; 6/11/83; U. Pa. debate; 3/30/83; Confirmation Hearing: Francis M. Mullen, Jr., Jud. Committee; 6/15/83; Floor Statement - Confirmation Hearing/ Jane Restani; 11/7/83; Floor Statement - Nomination of Kenneth L. Adelman, Arms Control Agency; 4/14/83; Senate Rules Committee, Federal Election Law; 5/17/83; Speech at Lorton Town Meeting; 9/9/83; Remarks: Freedom's Foundation Awards Program; Capitol; 6/15/83; Warner-Durrette Conversation/Va Beach; 11/5/83; Trans./Int. for "the Lawmakers" Senate Armed Services Committee; 10/12/83; Alex., Dedication of Torpedo Factory Art Center; 5/20/83; Senator John Warner Statement - Confirmation Hearing of Sherman E. Unger/Senate Committee on the Judiciary; 9/29/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner/Terrorist Attack on Marines in Lebanon; 10/24/83; Floor Statement - Armed Services Personnel Educational Travel; 11/3/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner on S. 237 S.1006; 11/1/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner/Announcement of Bowen Commission's Intent; 11/16/83; Floor Statement - Committee on Energy and Natural Resources- Strategic Minerals; 5/19/83; Speech by Senator John Warner to Commissioners of Revenue Association of VA; 11/15/83; Floor Statement - Battleship Missouri; 12/13/82; Governmental Affairs Conference, Washington; 5/11/83; Veterans Day Speech; 11/11/83; Untitled Folder: Introductory Remarks for Vice Pres. George Bush; 4/13/83; Hearing of Senate Judiciary comm./Re J.H. Wilkinson; 11/16/83; Interview- Henry Eason; It's Your Nation's Business; 5/19/83; Floor Statement - Kasten-Dole Compromise; 4/20/83; Senate committee on Energy and Natural Resources- Gas Hearings; 12/12/82; Floor Statement- Resolution to Commemorate Bicentennial of Treaty of Paris; 5/17/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner on S.J.Res. 196; 11/10/83; "Energy Independence" Speech; 8/9/83; Testimony of Senator John Warner/Committees of House and Senate on Veterans Affairs; 11/16/83; Luncheon w/Assorted General Contractors/Business Issues and Government Leasing; 10/7/83; Interview w/Chas. Wheeler/BBC/; 9/14/83; Launching-USS Yorktown- Pascagoula, Miss; 4/16/83; Floor Statement - Nat'l Tourism Week; 6/29/83; Luncheon Honoring House of Del./Va Beach; 11/5/83; Armed Forces Committee and Electronics Assn Shoreham-Americana Hotel-Washington, D.C.; 4/14/83; Floor Statement - Tech Vet School; 6/29/83; Subcommittee on International Trade (Finance Committee) Tariff on Apple Juice; 10/21/83; Speech- Young Republican Fed., Richmond, VA; 4/23/83; The Coal Industry; 8/9/83; Testimony- Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries; 4/21/83; Phone Interview/Post; 9/6/83; Opening Statement; JWW/Subcommittee on Energy and Mineral Resources; 11/15/83; Floor Statement - On S. 764, Air Travelers Act; 11/16/83; Speech at Opening of Henrico Co. Rep. HQ; 9/8/83; Floor Statement - S. 764- Air Traveler Security Act of 1983; 4/20/83; Immigration Reform and Control Act S. 529; 5/17/83; Floor Statement - To Put General Richardson's Address in CR; 7/83; Transcript/QA Press availability/James Watt; 10/7/83; Lawmakers; 7/14/83; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner/Scottsville Flood Control Project; 10/25/83; Subcommittee on Water Resources Committee Pub Works- Long Creek Canal and Tangier Island; 5/17/83; Public Hearing on Lake Gaston; 11/17/83; Floor Statement - Submits Sen. Byrd's Speech; 10/7/83; National Coal Assoc. Federal Affairs; 11/17/83; Press Conference I-66; 5/17/83; Appropriations Committee-Subcommittee on Interior Re. HR 1931 - S. 802- Parkway; 5/5/83; Veterans Affairs Committee Stmt of Harry N. Walters- Administrator Designee; 12/8/82; Floor Statement - on Amendment To Interior Appropriations Bill; 7/26/83; Floor Statement - National Retired Teachers Day; 8/4/83; Remarks of JWW Amherst 4th of July Celebration, "The American Flag"; 1983; Floor Statement - Nuclear Waste; 12/20/82; Floor Statement - Confirmation Hearing/Ross Buckley; 11/8/83; Senator John Warner Remarks/League of Women Voter Union Theological Seminary Richmond; 9/14/83; Floor Statement - Taxpayer Compliance and Withholding; 6/16/83; Floor Statement - Intro. To Mathias Speech on Palladian Architecture; 6/8/83; Interview-Mike Cozza, Jefferson Pilot; 5/6/83; Transcript/Interview Jim Bacon/Roanoke times/World New Port Dredging; 6/28/83; Interview w/Roger Lindberg (WVEC)/RE: Mil, Manpower level; 5/3/83; Interview w/Joel Brinkley, N.Y. Times/Lebanon Security; 11/4/83; Transcript/Phone Interview Tobacco/dairy; 10/7/83; Floor Statement - Forty one Years after Pearl Harbor; Dec. 7/1982; Senator John Warner Introduction of Amend to 1984 Treasury/Post Office Appropriations Bill- Moving Expense Reform; Rules Committee- Re: Purchase of Calendars; 12/9/82; Floor Statement - JWW/Burial of Indigent Veterans; 10/25/83; Hearing: Jud Committee, Southeast Low-Level Radioactive Waste Management Compact; 9/6/83; Floor Statement - Senate Tourism Caucus; 4/20/83; Speech by Gov. Robb/Report of Top Management of VA. Chamber of Commerce; 10/26/83; Transcript, Channel 4 Interview/Lebanon; 9/83; Hearing- Oversight Hearing on Strategic Petroleum Reserve; 5/6/83; Naming of US Courthouse, Norfolk, Va., Judge William E. Hoffman; 12/23/82; Interview w/Senator John Warner by Rose O'Connor, WTKR-TV; 11/14/83; Statement on Lyn M. Schlitt Nominations, Sen. Finance CMTE.; 6/14/83; Transcript/Phone Int./Va. Pilot Lake Gaston; 10/7/83; Testimony Before Aviation Subcommittee HS. Public Works Committee On S. 764 (Air Travelers Sec); 7/26/83; Dedication of Heritage Foundation; 10/3/83; Untitled Folder: 5/16/83; Interview- Karlyn Barker, Washington Post; 4/21/83; Floor Statement - TV Coverage of Senate Proceedings; 12/23/82; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner on US Coal Exports to Japan; 10/27/83; Remarks of JWW/Hampton Institute Convocation; 9/11/83; News Release on JWW urging Rededication to Freedom/11/12/83; Interview: w/Ed Prina, Copley News Serv. Re: Military manpower; 5/6/83; Armed Services Committee Intro. C. Cox, Assistant Secretary of the Navy; 5/24/83; Introductory remarks for Admiral Hyman Rickover Award Ceremony; 11/1/83; VA Savings and Loan League Speech, VA Beach; 6/17/83; Floor Statement - JWW/Advance Procurement SN SSN 688 Submarines; 11/8/83; Subcommittee on Education, Art and Humanities; 4/8/83; Confirmation Hearing- Moody Tidwell Judge- US Claims Court; 5/4/83; Opening Statement: JWW/Subcommittee on Energy and Mineral Resources 11/10/83; Floor Statement - Soviet Shooting of Korean Flt. 007; 9/14/83; Floor Statement - on H.R. 1646 RR Retirement Solvency; 8/2/83; Extra copies of Staggers Act Testimony; Remarks on JWW American Federation of Government Employees AFL/CIO; 8/4/83; Speech- McLean, Fairfax County Arbor Day Celebration; 4/25/83; Floor Statement - Re: UP Amendment 1484 to H.R. 6211- Multi-employer's Pension Amendment Act of 1980; 12/16/82; Floor Statement - of Senator John Warner/US coal Exports to Japan; 10/28/83; Big Stone Gap, Wise, Norton, Wash, DC; 4/23/83; Interview: ABC; 7/8/83; Floor Statement - Retirement of Albert A Applegate; 12/20/82; Satellite Speech to the Norfolk Chamber of Commerce; 1/5/83; Floor Statement - MX Missile; 5/25/83; Atoka Speech; 9/10/83; Floor Statement - H.Con.Res. 153 - Statue of Martin Luther King; 12/20/82; Interview- Bill Woods- Virginian Pilot- MX- Midgetman; 4/25/83; Floor Statement - Low Altitude Reconnaissance Cameras- 12/18/1982
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings and Warner Speeches, 2/28/1978-12/31/1996 (Box 191)
    To Sales Execs at Jefferson Club Roanoke/Free Enter; 3/8/83; Untitled Folder: Floor Statement- Amend the Tariff Schedule of the United States to Impose a Duty on Apple and Pear Juice; 2/3/83; Subcommittee on Manpower and Personnel; 3/8/83; Interview: W/Pat Towell, Congressional Quarterly; 3/9/83; 12 folders of press clippings grouped by date.; GW PRKWY S. 802; 3/11/83; Floor Statement - Strategic Nuclear Threat; 3/23/83; The Northern Virginia Women's History Coalition; 3/8/83; Interview- Tara St. John- World Perspectives- Re: Def Budget, Arms Control Port Legis; 2/23/83; Interview: News Availability/U.Va.; 3/7/83; Greenspan Comm. Full retirement for Fed. Workers from 55 to 65; Assoc Gen Contractors of VA. Convention Awards Lunch- Homestead, Hot Springs, Va; 1/22/83; Untitled Folder: Election Law Hearing; 1/26/83; Interview- George Wilson- Washington Post- Warner Proposal on Reduction in End Strength; 2/22/83; Interview- Nancy Bradsher, Watch on Washington; 3/16/83; Floor Statement - Senate Amendment #512, New Fed Employees in Social Security, 3/18/1983; Floor Statement - Erosion Control Projects in the Chesapeake Bay; 1/26/83; 3/8/83; Interview- Joe Shapiro, U.S. News and World Report; 2/15/83; Dulles Toll Road Groundbreaking Ceremony; 1/29/83; Lions Club; 3/83; Speech: ADM. Rickover Dinner w/3 Presidents; Sheraton, D.C.; 2/28/78; Interview- WTAR Radio, Norfolk; 3/2/83; Floor Statement - Enterprise Zone Employment & Develop Act of 1983; 3/18/83; Commerce- Confirmation Hearing for Helen Marie Taylor- Bd. Dir. Pub Broad; 2/4/83; Cumberland, Cumberland Repls.; 3/15/1983; Floor Statement - George Washington Parkway, Va; 3/9/83; Lincoln Club Dinner, Vienna, VA; 2/4/83; Mining and Reclamation Council of America; 3/22/83; Speech at FT. Myer; 3/3/83; Statement on State of the Union; 1/25/83; Floor Statement - Commission on the Centennial of The Civil Service; 3/14/83; 10% Withholding Requirement Savings Interest and Investment Dividends; 2/10/83; Vepcopac, Richmond; 3/11/83; Untitled Folder: "Coal Slurry Pipeline Act"- S.267; 3/14/83; Floor Statement- Air Travelers Security Act of 1983; 3/10/83; Judiciary Committee- Appointment Alfred S. Regnery - Admin. Juvenile Justice & Deliq. Prev. - Department of Justice; 4/6/83
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 1/1/2000-8/31/2001 (Box 192)
    4 folders of press clippings from August, Sept, Nov, and Dec of 2000; Loose Paper: misc. press clippings, Warner press releases, and legislative copies; 19 bundles of press clipping packets grouped weekly
  - Dept. P: Scott - Speeches and Background Materials, 1/1/1968-12/31/1993 (Box 193)
    Talking Points for Crossfire [binder]; Abortion Votes 1979--1989 [binder]; Memos and Correspondence regarding speaking engagement at the Washington County Chamber of Commerce [binder]; Press Releases (85-88) EPW [binder]; Military-Soldier-War Quotations [binder]; United Citizens, Nixon-Agnew [binder]; Press releases, talking points, etc. [binder]; Speech writing materials on various topics including Air/Space Extension, Balanced Budget/Economy, Crime, Defense/Foreign Policy, GOP, Heath/Education, Highways, Property Rights, Speech, United Nations, etc. [binder]; Speech writing materials on various topics including Budget and Auburn Dam [binder]; United Citizens, Nixon-Agnew, Report 10-5-68 [binder]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, Press Releases, 1/1/1989-12/31/1996 (Box 194)
    1996: 2/1-3/7 clippings; 1996: 1/22-31 clippings; 1996: 1/1-7 clippings; 1996: 1/8-14 clippings; 1995: 12/1-7 clippings [loose]; 1995: 11/1-7 clippings [loose]; 1996: 3/15-21 clippings; Press Releases 1989 [binder]; 1996: 1/15-21 clippings; Sen. Warner's Quote Book (clippings) [binder]; 1995: 11/22-31 clippings [loose]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 1/1/1999-2/12/1999 (Box 195)
    30 packets of press clippings, arranged in reverse chronological order
  - Dept. P: Scott - Releases and Clippings related to Louisiana Election, 1/1/1996-12/31/1997 (Box 196)
    Press Clippings on the Investigation of the Election of Louisiana Senator Mary Landrieu, Vol. II-Book 2 (Sept. 1997-Dec. 1997 [binder]; 1997 Releases [binder]; Untitled Binder: Press Releases 1996; Press Clippings on the Investigation of the Louisiana Senator Mary Landrieu, Vol. II-Book 1 (1/1997-8/1997) [binder]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Speeches, interview transcripts, and correspondence, 1/1/1974-12/31/1995 (Box 197)
    Transcripts - 8/1984; Written Requests (media, congrats, welcomes, etc.); Transcripts - 7/1984; Transcripts - 101984; LAIRD; 1982 Microfilm Index; Transcripts - 9/1984; Transcripts - 6/1984; Straight Remarks (cancelled); Foreword for Military Manual; Press Letters; Loose papers: speeches; Untitled: clippings and correspondence; Background for Warner Bio; GMV Speech 11-16-88; Transcripts - 11/1984; 1983 Microfilm Index
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 2/1/1999-4/1/1999 (Box 198)
    49 packets of press clippings, arranged by date
  - Dept. P: Scott - Press Clippings, 4/1/1997-12/31/1997 (Box 199)
    9 folders of political mention clippings, April-December 1997
  - Dept. P: Scott - Voting Records and Floor Statements, 1/1/1979-12/31/1986 (Box 200)
    Warner Record 1985 [binder]; Warner Record-6/1984 [binder]; Record Votes-1981, 1982, 1983 [binder]; Senator John Warner Voting Record, 79-80-81 [binder]; Floor Statements 1986 [binder]; JWW Missed Votes, 97th & 98th, -84-, (82/83) [binder]
  - Dept. P: Scott - Voting Record, Floor Statements, Grant Notices, 1/1/1986-12/31/1992 (Box 201)
    Floor Statements, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, Continued [binder]; Grant Notices, 1986 [binder]; Record Vote Analysis, 102nd Congress, 2nd Session, Press
  - Dept. L: CY -Judge Files, Includes correspondence, speeches, press releases, schedules, 1/1/1995-12/31/1998 (Box 202)
    JW Schedules-Week; Subs-Teaming; Education Stuff; T-mond B-Day; Energy and Water; ACITIC- VA Tech; LOB Culpepper; CRS on Internet; Bosnia/NATO/Europe; Transport/WW Brigade; Amers Tax Reform; Miscellaneous Articles; BASC Releases 99; Accomplishments 105th Congress, 1st Session; Tobacco; NEA; VA Press News; Senate Barber; State of Union 1-98; Laptops; Sabato Roast; EDA/Development/Westmoreland/Tapahook 5-98; Berlin Airlift; Ralston; Defense/SASC; JW Bio. D's; Lorton; T. Vaughn and Const. File; Beth George; Loose articles; Cohen Trip, 2-98, Face CBS; Press Requests; Juvenile Justice; SBA Small Business; Speeches; Ethics/Lobby/MCI $; USS Wisconsin; Vets Burial Bones; Keagan A-Port; High Tech; Depots, N. News; VA D-Day Ceremony 11/97; Newt-Speaker File, Marietta 1-98 speech, CHC 1-98 speech; ATF-JW; ANC Waivers; DoD Authorization 1997
  - Dept. L: CY-Correspondence, Clippings and Reference Materials, 1/1/1987-12/31/2002 (Box 203)
    Pres. Cabinet Nominees [presentation folder]; McNulty; Ashcroft; James Younger; Mental Health/Terrorism; Ricky Ray; Chavez; Tobacco [presentation folder]; Thompson; Rod Paige; Ted Olson, 4/5/2001; Brownlee; Barnhart; Ombudsman [presentation folder]; Brian James
  - Dept. L: Shari -Red Star Letters, 105th Congress, Bills, Correspondence, Floor Statements and Mail Reports, 1/1/1997-12/31/2000 (Box 204)
    Weekly Mail Reports, 1997; 105th Mail Reports, 1998; 105th Dear Colleagues - Cosigned; 105th Dear Colleagues - Miscellaneous; 105th Floor Statements, 1997; Weekly Mail Reports, 2000; 105th Floor Statements, 1998; 105th No Position; 105th UC's-Cosponsor of JW Legislation; 105th Dear Colleagues - Senator John Warner; 105th Sponsor/Cosponsored
  - Dept. L: Chris Y- Education, 1/1/1999-12/31/2001 (Box 205)
    ESEA: Math and Science; ESEA; ESEA: My Notes; ESEA: Class Size; ESEA: Teacher Liability; ESEA: Floor Students last day; ESEA: Background; ESEA: VA Specific background; ESEA: 21st Century Community Learning Center; ESEA: Homeless/LEP; ESEA: School Counseling; ESEA Group Views; ESEA: Magnet Schools; ESEA: Title I; ESEA: Straight A's
  - Dept. L: Chris Y.- Education, No Child Left behind Act, Roger Gregory nomination to the 4th Circuit court, 1/1/2000-12/31/2001 (Box 206)
    The Power of Creativity: VSA arts, 10/2000 [VHS]; Loose paper- No child left behind bill, 2001; ESEA [presentation folder]; Roger Gregory
  - Dept. A: Doriene -Admin. Chronological Files, 1/1/2000-12/31/2000 (Box 207)
    8/2000; College Admissions; 5/2000; 9/2000; 6/2000; 4/2000; 11/2000; 2/2000; 7/2000; 10/2000; 3/2000; 12/2000; 1/2000
  - Dept. A: Doriene -White House Recommendation Files, 1/1/2002-12/31/2002 (Box 208)
    67 folders, mainly correspondence, arranged alphabetically by last name
  - Dept. L: 1995 Small Business Hearings, tobacco, 1/1/1991-12/31/2000 (Box 209)
    Tobacco Warehouse; Tobacco-OSHA Regulations, Labor Department; Mike; Loose clippings and correspondence re: tobacco; SBC Hubzones; Loose Papers: reference material re: small businesses; Loose Papers: clippings and correspondence re: small businesses; NASCAR; Loose clippings and correspondence re: tobacco; Tobacco Row- Urban Revitalization
  - Dept. L: Tobacco Issues, 1/1/1995-12/31/1998 (Box 210)
    Info Regarding Tobacco Suits; Briefing Book: The Food and Drug Administration and Tobacco Regulation [portfolio folder]; Tobacco 2nd Hand Smoke:; Tobacco: Tobacco Issues 103rd, Cigarettes [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: Small Business Comm. Issues, 1/1/1996-12/31/1998 (Box 211)
    Loose Papers: Notes, Business cards, Faxes, Statements, Correspondence; S.942 Mr. Warner--Markup materials; Untitled Portfolio: Dredging Contractors of America; Untitled Folder: Correspondence, Faxes; Small Business-S04 program-HR3719; Small Business-HUB Zones-S.1574; Northrup; 06/05/96--Small Business Agenda, Stewart Verdery/Mr. Warner; 06/04/98--Oversight of SBIR Program Chas Phillips/Mr. Warner; Reston Chamber; Virginia Small Business Awards Luncheon [binder]
  - Dept. A: Schedule Back-up Files, 1/1/1998-5/31/1998 (Box 212)
    140 Daily Schedule Files, arranged chronologically
  - Dept. A: Liz Taylor Press articles, 1/1/1980-12/31/1983 (Box 213)
    Speech Material; Untitled Envelope: articles and press releases; Loose Paper: speech with research material; Articles [bag]; Speaker's package on Nuclear Arms and Arms Control [binder]; Loose Paper: articles; Untitled: Colston A. Lewis; Zumwalt file [envelope]; Untitled Envelope: articles; Untitled: Speech at Segregated School; Defense; Loose Paper: articles, press releases, booklet with photographs of Liz Taylor and Senator, and correspondence; Land Fairfax Human resources council; Loose Papers: articles
  - Dept. A: Voting Record, Record on Issues, and Contribution Reports, 1/1/1979-12/31/1988 (Box 214)
    Warner: Leadership for Virginia [binder]; Warner Record [binder]; Warner Record Addendum; Senator John Warner Voting Record- 1987 [binder]; Voting Record 1985 [binder]; The Warner Record- 1987 [binder]; Warner Record 1986 [binder]; FEC Report, 1st Quarter [binder]
  - Dept. L: EPW Public Works Issues, 1/1/1995-12/31/1999 (Box 215)
    SEPA/PMAS; Arts and Humanities; Aid- Federal Triangle; PMA; Shenandoah National Park; Historic Preservation; Regulatory Reform; Rural Electric; GSA Projects; Untitled: congressional material/speech; Security in Federal Buildings; Lane View Elementary School
  - Dept. L: EPW Committee, Water Resources (WRDA), 1/1/1998-12/31/1999 (Box 216)
    WRDA 1998: loose paper and reference materials, correspondence, and testimonies [presentation folder]; WRDA 98: loose paper and reference materials, correspondence, and legislation [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: EPW Committee, Water Resources (WRDA), 1/1/1998-12/31/1999 (Box 217)